Sandra
Lewes's frogs haven't sold yet
What makes you think he'll lose money
You really don't know
what kind of person your son is
He's just not cut out for success
You
Enough
It's my own bad luck
to marry my daughter into
your Liu family
Lewes
Close your farm as soon as possible
and keep working for Daniel
Exactly
Your brother-in-law
might pay you less
but at least you won't have to
lose your own money
Stop messing around
Lewes
If all else fails
you can just come to my place
You can be Zhibin's assistant
Clean up frog droppings
Keep an eye on the greenhouse
I'll pay you eighty a day
You
Thanks for your kindness
But
I have confidence
in my frogs
I'm done drinking
I've got work at the farm
We'll be leaving first
Mom, Dad, let's go
Lewes
is so ungrateful
He's drowning in debt
Let's see how he pays it off
What did the Liu family do
to deserve this
Let him be smug
for a while
Daniel's batch
has reached the critical fattening stage
Without my timely adjustment
on feed and water temperature
more than half of his frogs will die
Forget profit
even their three million
will be gone
Mom, Dad
I'm sorry
for making you
suffer this humiliation today
A little humiliation doesn't matter
Lewes
We believe in you
You'll succeed
Once you make money
we'll hold our heads high
In one month at most
we'll extract the forest frog oil and ship it out
I will make sure
no one dares to look down on us anymore
We believe in you